I mean welcome dancer
저 텐션이 너무 낮아요 아니 아니 좋아
gives that Old Hollywood vibe I would love Glam
우리가 많이 해 본 적 아는 스타일 있잖아 마돈나 스타일을 해
달라 그냥 내가 예쁘게 할게 그냥 그럼 되잖아 매력을 입체에서
gives that Old Hollywood vibe it's giving Hollywood Old Hollywood
I would love glam oh my God oh retired mom
good morning
너가 얼마나 바뀌었는지 내가 어 thank you so much everybody
thank you 아이고 우리 안녕 빠이빠이 잘 먹겠습니다 빠이 안녕 애가
엄마 어 엄마 갈려가다가 지금 낙갈이 낙갈이가
놀랬어 낙갈이 말대가 아님인데 애기들은
좀 그렇더라고 엄마가 갑자기 너무 나왔어요 그러니까 그렇죠 다른 사람
같으니까 다른
사람 같으니까 아무튼 우리 다 고생하셨습니다 고생하셨습니다
자 우리 이걸로 하죠 주먹 자 짠짠짠짠 꽃단장
아유 이리 와 끝까지 어색하다 해
아우 허리야 내가요
너 안에 치킨 하나만 먹어봐 어 치킨 있어요 진짜 너만 안 먹었거든 진짜
너무 맛있다 그거 내가 너무
맛있어 너게 너게 아우야 먹어야 되지 아니 여기
거의 새 것처럼 보이는 게 있는데 이거 뭐야 근데 안 먹었다
응 야 치킨
맛있지 왜 치킨 이거 아니 응 아 진짜 열심히 사 왔는데 아무도 못
먹으니까 이게 속상하더라 아 먹을 속상하더라 아 먹을 수가 없어 진짜
먹을
수가 없어서
아
우리 뭐 먹읍시다 이거 뭐야 이거는 있을까 그 다 샌드위치 샌드위치
밥을 안 먹었나 음
저는 그냥 시간이
없는데 모발이 너무
다 다른 거예요 왜냐면 너무 다양정이니까 두상 세이프 다 다른 거예요
그래서 와 이거는 미션이다 그 다음부터는
정신이 없어서 그냥 막 막 달린
거예요 제가 솔직히 제가 힘들다는 얘기를 진짜 잘
안 하거든요 절대 안 해요 근데 아우 식사 사치라고 생각했어요 와 이거
이거 왜 먹어 지금 이거 해야 되는데 걱정돼서 밥도 안 넘어가요 아
근데 한번 어 좀 연구를 좀 해보자 먹을 수 있는 방법을
강구를 한번 해보자
근데 좀 땡겨도 될 거 같애 한 한 시간 정도 잡아도 될 거 같애 그쵸
메이크업이요 응응 아니까 실제로 하는 건 내일이 여섯
명이죠 응응 그러면 아 우리 열 시부터 한다고 해도 한 시간은
안 될 거 같애 한 시간 이십 분 정도 걸릴 거 같애요 하는데 메이크업
에 메이크업 왜냐면 마지막 파이널 그
체크가 있어 가지고 레온은 어땠어 오늘 두 두 명 했으니까
근데 세 명
하면은 확실히 그 힘은 들 거 같은데
살짝 이제 저 정리할 시간이라든지 뭐 이런 게 좀 부족한 거 같아 에
내가 사용했던 브러쉬나 이런
것들 좀 한번 싹 정리하고 이제 깨끗한 상태로 모시고 싶은데 보는 앞에서
막 하고 막 지우고 이런 거라 음
그리고 중간중간 뭐 조금 진짜 뭐
지 집어 먹을 시간도 지금 오늘은 없었거든 혹시
저 페어와 메이크업 하는데 얼마 걸렸어 아까 시간이요 시간도 체크 못
한 거 있죠 그러니까 시간 체크 못 하셨구나 그냥
했어 막 빨리 무조건 저도 지금 얼마 걸렸는지 모르죠
원래 미용실은 딱 타이밍이 있어서 그거
맞춰서 아웃 타이밍 시간까지 해서 보내긴 하는데 그니까 그거를 어떻게
보면 내가 체크를 해줘야 되는 거잖아 원래
종이 체수 체크 리스트가 있거든요 들어온
시간 나가야 될 시간 선배님이 체크를 해주셔야 되고 뭐
한 십 십분 전쯤
들어가서 십 십분 남았습니다 이 정도까지 해
주시면 될 거 같은데 삼 삼십분 전부터
십분 타임을 얘기해 주는게 좋아요 아 아
그 첫날이어서 뭐
그랬겠지만 선생님들도 이제 그 하루 종일 어 서서 정말 쉬는
시간 없이 계속하는데
진짜 십분씩도 시간이
안 돼 가지고 첫날부터 해서 폰이 선생님 아예 못 먹었고
사실은 그게 좀 제일 마음에 걸렸던 거 같아요
자 가실까요 이제 다 갈아입었죠
네 가자 가자 가자 수고하셨습니다 아우 고생하셨습니다
아우 아 근데 진짜 잘하시더라 두 분 다 감사합니다 네
굿모닝
안녕하세요 우와 하이 아 어제
배고팠던 기억이 있 있었나 봐요
아침을 먹어야 된다니까 예 지금 드실래요 네 계란 드실래 아니면은 뭐
막 때려 넣어야 돼 어 막 때려 넣어야 돼 때려 넣어야 된다고 그냥 지금
당장 그러면은 나도
라면 좀 먹을래
아침을
먹어야 된다니까 맛있다 맛없나 음
그니까 나도 지금 똑같은 맛을 먹었거든 근데 좀
다르지 근데 김치 맛있어요 아니 어제 너무 배가 고픈 거예요 너무 배가
고파 가지고 지금 억지로 그냥 막 나도 때려 사육하고 있어 나 자신을
어 아니 우리 점심은
못
먹을 수도
있을 것 같아 오늘 좀 많이 먹어요 아 저 식사 시간 드릴 거예요
정말요 예 제가 따로
다 그냥 콜해서 억지로라도 그냥 식사 시간도 그냥 쏙
시켜요 아 오늘 제가 다 밥 먹게 해 드리겠습니다 와
음 밥 시간 다 드릴게요 십오분 어때요 십오분
좋아요 아 십오분이면은 충분하지 디저트까지 먹죠 삼십분 간격으로 온다고
oh my God
that's insane hahaha 자 다 오셨나요 들어오시죠
아이구 아 이거 잘했어
님 오늘도 잘 부탁드립니다 우리의 업장님 다 짠 명차 가져갔으거
스타일링이고 드라이기 그다음에 스타일링이고 여기는 아이론
엎지마 어디서 났어 여기서
아
아 고마워 나는 그냥 이렇게 하고 한번 접으면 아
어 그래 되겠다 그럼 끈이 안 보여 이게 바로 호텔 경영 스타일
어허 그렇게 배웠어요 아
그리고 이런 데서 실제로는 몰랐지만 이런 데서 실제로는 몰랐지만
ㅎㅎ 저 뿌리기 씨
또 이거 참 챙겼어
또 네 여기 이제 스탭용 여기 이거 이거 한국에서 어떻게 사
왔어요 다 다 다 챙겨 왔어요 아이고 자 오픈 십분
전입니다 아 아 아 들리시나요 어우 잘 들려요
언니 우리 제가 첫 번째로 맞이할 흥룡이 누구예요
보시는 아 네 레이철 킴인데 첫 번째 분은 미국 분이신데 이거야 지금 열시
반부터 삼십 분 간격으로 올 거야 그니까 오자마자 그냥 바로
옷 까운 갈아입히께 네
열한 시에 들어오면 회화를 열두 시까지 하고 열두 시 할 때쯤에
이때 내가 머리 풀어주고 여기 식사가 오면 손이가
제일 먼저 밥을 먹을 수 있겠다
완벽해 흐 완벽해 흐 됐어 이십구 분
hello you first queen you're the it's okay hahaha you should come over
something sounds like something sounds like it's
like
안녕하세요
하이 어서 오세요 어서 오세요 환영합니다 환영합니다 환영합니다
your name is Kelly my name is Kelly hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
nice to meet you nice to meet you
Kelly hi Kelly
ah I'm Grace Grace Grace hello Kelly nice to meet you and Grace ah
also Grace can I have a seat eh come on
hi I'm Leo I'm your makeup artist today hello yeah
I'm today your hair Trista nice to meet you Trista nice to meet you
nice to meet you guys
I'm your makeup artist today hello I love your hair so pretty
hi nice to meet you
nice to meet you do you speak Korean
a little bit a little bit a little bit
you gonna choose drink
what about the snacks
Yakult Yakult
you like it have you tried it
oh pronunciation is so good
Yakult correct oh
have you tried this before I love Yakult
have no makeup on
I'm so excited to transformation yeah
I'm excited
are you ready
화장 재밌겠다 이분 맞아 그냥 스폰 재밌겠다 느낌이 온다요
예 어 헬로 켈리 하우 아루 유
good so I am a manager I'm a minion park
I know who you are I know who you are
did you watch my show yes yes which one which one did you watch um
I really like um
Secretary Kim secretary ah
yes secretary Kim became a manager here yeah
so can you tell me what brings you here you know
tell me about your story a little
um I really like K pop K drama you know
I can see that um and
I don't like I was telling them that I used to be a trainee for
a girl group
oh
so like since it was during Covid
we kind of had like a online thing
they were going to like bring me there but
alright I didn't go yeah yeah I understand that
I actually like got an opportunity to be a trainee for Black Swan
and I became one of the finalists but I ended up not going
cause like we couldn't figure out like my visa and everything
oh so I ended up not doing it
um so after that I took a break from like K pop period
so I was like mad like I was sad and I couldn't go
yeah I bet
I think that field is where like my heart lies
at the same time I feel like everything happens for a reason
and that more opportunities will come if it's meant to be you know
yeah I understand that
so but you're still K
you know Idol lover right
yes yes
yeah it's still going on more
yes and have you ever been to
you know K Salon or
no I haven't
I really wanted to like try it uh huh
I was a K pop trainee years ago
but I didn't end up doing that
so I thought it would be really cool to dress up in that style
to see like what if what if
you know what it would have looked like if I did do it
I think this was like a really cool opportunity
something like this it won't happen again
you know so I wanted to do it anyway
so any style that you you know thought about anything
not really well
kind of like I have like idols I really like
and they are all like girl crush concepts
like I really like Blackpink's Jenny
oh Jenny's here
uh huh Blackpink's Jenny
yeah but
I think like for my look I don't know if it fits that
we can we can make it everyone
you know he's just magician yeah
maybe we should find a bright color for her
yes I know her style
so if you want I can transform like that yeah
it looks maybe gonna be good
but I recommend you the dewy
dewy lips over lips yeah
and she needs to cover her face like a very lightweight okay
lightweight but full coverage yes
because thick foundation looks not really good
I don't like that you know
just believe us you know
we can make it I do I believe
let's make her a princess
oh my God I'm gonna fly away
it's like magic so cool
oh my God period
I'm glowing yeah wow
it's very comfy it is
do you love it I do
I've never seen anything like this before
it's really as uh this classic in Korea
hmm
let's go what's going on
just relax just relax
I've never seen anything like that before
I was like wow
this is so cool
have you done this before
reclining chair no
that's why I was like ah
what's happening hahaha yes
it's very special today I give you a massage
ooh I'm gonna fall asleep if you do that
it's pretty strong how's the pressure
good it's good yeah
OK I'm very hard headed
return to your chairs
OK
혹시 혹시 혹시 말리는 거 오래 걸리나요
메이크업 먼저 하면 안 돼요 근데 헤어 먼저 하라고 돼 있어요 찍을 거예요
아 헤어 아예 먼저 메이크업 한 먼저 하고 싶긴 한데
나도 메이크업 먼저 하고 싶긴 한데
예 왜 메 원장님 원장님 네 혹시 그 메이크업 먼저 해도 되나요 저분
저희는 약간 메이크업을
먼저 하면 더 수월하거든요 첫 번째 분 네 헤어가 먼저 돼 있긴 한데 네
순서상 네 그렇게 하셔도 돼요
아 네 우선 그렇게 할게요 네 첫 번째 분이죠 네
저 뭐 메이크업 먼저
한 할게요 혹시
그 스킨케어 하는 동안 머리 같이 말리면 더 빠를 거 같아서 어 예 네
그렇게 메이크업 먼저 하기로 했어요 네
어 아 do you like a B Style
スケジュールを決めておきますよ
let's go to make a room チャイチャイワオ
イェーアーアイハッピーウェルカムアイハッピ
ーイェーワオウェルカムアイハッ
ピーイェーワオ
I've never been into
a place where like all the makeups laid out like that
I was like wow yeah sit down please thank you wow you have everything
so many products haha
and this is mask bag and it's really good for the
oh I like the smell yeah and cooling
refreshing refreshing and refreshing
what do you say Korean she want it right she want it yes she want it
that's what I feel
I think yours intro extrovert right
actually when I did the test I was I m B t I yeah
I N t P I N t P
I N t P oh my God
have you tried it yeah
but I think I'm introvert and I disguise as extrovert oh
cause if it's quiet I can't shut up hahaha
wash your face it's really cool
oh it is gone
it is really cool yeah
it's like magic yeah
it's really important your sensitive skin
woah hahaha
woah hahaha woah
hahaha
I think you got a like positive energy
sometimes it's too much for people
but I love it
어 you got it
에너지가 잘 맞았던 거 같아요 나 이 친구 너무 고마워요 진짜
왜냐면은 저 되게 이성향이거든요 여기서 하루 종일
뭔가 이 팀들과 함께 하면서 저의 이런 길을 사실 조금 누르고 있어요
왜냐면은 너무
나대고 싶지 않아서
근데 이 친구랑 같이만 슬레이 슬레이 슬레이 슬레이 너무 기쁜 거예요
웰컴
예
my period my own power period period period period
oh I love your lashes thank you
by Ella for us copper
so cool I'm watching a professional in his natural habitat right now
period
okay concealer first
the lightweight concealer first and cushion
I've been doing it backwards
foundation like cushion and then concealer
okay forehead look at the forehead this one
I'm glowing yeah oh wow I do look very different
oh my god I love your skin now look at your skin
you fixed it yes Omg
I've never I haven't seen it this clear since I was like really 15
haha
it's like magic covered everything
okay
and next liner uh shadow
okay I'll be showing you the palette today
with this palette even if you are new to makeup
I can show you how to uh makeup with just one palette ooh
yeah it can helps highlighter
contour blusher wow everything
everything yeah you can do this with this one
just one palette okay okay
like a shading blush with this palette again
highlighter
that's crazy all you need is the one palette and everything's yeah
that's so cool it's only one
oh
I love this colour
oh my God you are really good with pink
you are pink person pink person
the little girl in me is so happy that you said yeah
let's Whip Mascara
아이돌 하면은 사실 뭐 또 지금은 스타일들이 너무나 다양해졌지만
아이돌 그룹에 좀 또 포인트 중에 하나가 가락 솜씨 없이 하잖아요
뭔가 이렇게 떨망하게 또 아이돌스럽게 언저드려야지 생각이 그냥 들었어요
do you use the fake lashes usually
I've never used fake lashes okay I need to take off my mascara I've
got a fake lashes and I've got a mascara and I'm gonna
take off my mascara that's what
I'm gonna do
아 그게
낼 거 같죠 저 제 생각이 그래요 왜냐면
지금 손으로 써봐도 너무 풍부해서 맞아 많이 할 필요 없어요 너무 많이
하면 또 그림 자제할 수도 있으니까
OK lashes please
may I look down please
you already have perfect lashes so just mascara thank you
yeah
I take care of my lashes cause I don't like wearing makeup usually
wow
yeah let's just look amazing
one by one
we are K beauty style right
that's cool 사실 그 포인트를 그거 거기서
가져온 거예요 제가 한국에서 미리 그 아이돌
메이크업을 외국인 모델 서배를 해서 연습을 하고 왔어요 그걸
보고서 아 외국인
분들은 우리나라라 분들처럼 이렇게 하나하나 심을 필요가 없구나
왜냐면 본인은 성능습이 오락기 있고 소심하니까
그거 찝어드리면 되겠구나
I see girls put lashes on that look like this
right yeah but you already have the perfect lashes
so just tweeze them
wow it's like this one oh my God I'm gonna fly away yeah hahaha
where are you where are you
oh so funny
oh my God look at her that's crazy oh my God ha ha ha who is she
아이돌 스타예요 진짜 리얼리 진짜 네 끝났어요 근데 진짜 아이돌이다
oh let's go let's go she is coming
your friend is coming finally
oh my God oh my God 우리 그레이스 어떡해 왜
그레이스 버리고 남자친구랑 데이트하러 갈
거래요 남자친구랑 데이트하러 갈 거래요 oh my God
she's gonna go on a date after this you made it like a two hours
oh my God
온다 온다 oh my
God
this is mine this is mine this is mine
I used to be a trainee for a girl group all the dumb things that
oh oh
oh my gosh she's a little girl oh my gosh
thank you babe hahaha slay queen slay queen hahaha
come and walk this way hey baby walk this way
this is ponytail
oh nice
자기 레트로로 다시 돌아서 아이돌 스타일 진짜 리얼리
it would be cool to know what I could have been dressed in or like
styled in if I were to pursue that
slay queen hahaha
oh my God I love it wait it looks so good on you hahaha
can I see your lashes he literally like
oh my God wait these are your natural lashes yeah
it's her it's her lashes wow
you look so good so good you look so beautiful oh my God
I think this was a very good experience
I do style it's really really it's really
pretty ready for the stage hahaha oh
it's weird like saying that I feel like but it definitely
it's it feels very like
empowering in a way like to be like all dressed up I do 10
out of 10 10 10
thank you so much thank you so much have a good day thank you bye
who's you who are you going on a date with
Eric later like Eric 6 haha
Kimmy so pretty
oh hello hi oh hello hi
아 하이
어서 오세요 당장에 오신 것을 환영합니다 아 나이스
미트 유 하이 레이철 레이철 킹 hi
she is a mother my mom ah
my mom you look like sister momma 너무 예뻐요
oh no I know her hahaha
do you know me yeah oh really say hello like a hello yeah oh
hahaha 어 땡큐 어머니
왜 이렇게 이뻐요 어머니 잘하시네요 엄마는 한국 아
can you speak Korean Sir 잠깐만 잠깐만 잠깐만 잠깐만 잠깐만 아
진짜 아 감사합니다
so
are you ready for the consultation I'm ready yes yes please follow me
please have a seat here
so I heard that you're a model yes so I'm a plus size model
so I represent girls who are like a little bit bigger or curvy
it's so cool
fashion and beauty yes oh
wow so yeah I'm here because I'm very used to doing like
American style hair American style makeup
so because I have a Korean face maybe I can learn some new techniques
to enhance my features that are Korean oh wait wait are you
half I'm half Korean oh really oh not an appa Miguk's ah
not an oma hang ah
I love like cause I feel like especially like with Asian eyes
you want them to like pop and make them look
bigger so like I definitely like styles that
accentuate the eyes and make them look bigger than they actually are
I like your eyelashes a lot like this style
uh huh you love it it's like a baby doll yeah right
I you you love it uh huh OK
hi my name is Rachel Pearl the flurry
I live in Brooklyn New York and I'm a full time model
specifically plus size model and I'm 33 years old
I started modeling when I was about
19 or 20 years old they needed a lot of diversity plus size modeling
had just started to become popular
so I'm one of the very few Korean plus size models
at least in New York
I'm so used to doing Western American style beauty
I wanted to try something new specifically Korean beauty
so I asked for
like a Korean style makeup look and a Korean style haircut
you can use the the product
지우고 샴푸 해야겠죠 네 어 네 세한 세한 밴드나 아니면 어 있어요 어
should I hold it
ㅎㅎ 이렇게 or do you have a Bobby pin
you'll you'll think clip 아 아 예 네 오케이 오케이
네이스
oh
come this way
oh have a seat OK
well you're you have baby face yeah you got good skin
ah
wow it's such a different feeling oh yeah I love it
relax
are you alright is it comfortable yeah OK
we're gonna put your pack first mm hmm yeah
why why are you laughing like that it looks cold no
버블 없어야 돼 이거 완벽하게
네 부탁해요 네
Rachel how's the temperature it's alright uh huh I'm Kenshina
I'm Kenshina
just let me know if it's hot OK
Rachel mm hmm lawyer haha ah I was lawyer yeah right
no no
major what does that mean like extraordinary attorney you the drama
oh yeah the show
I think your mom saw it
wait so you were in a show yeah but you're also a hairstylist no
this is my first time I just love it yeah
you just Learned how to do it
I love it
do you know you're my second customer
you know
haha
oh my ah
it was big secret it was my secret ah
oh my God
제 두 번째 제가 두 번째 강겨프는 so you're an actor yeah in Korea yeah
do you like it yeah I love it
and I and I love this one too I this this job
ah it was my top secret ah you know
yes
I did my best you did oh my God
I think you did I think you did a good job I don't know what I
whoo I'm done
I did my best was that hard
I don't know how how did you feel you feel like professional
kind yes haha maybe oh you did it oh my God yes it felt professional
okay have a seat
꼭 같이 만나요 드림 응
it's very strong mm hmm
it's very powerful so it's very quickly dry and then lastly
I'm getting
more volume oh that's good yeah make the volume I love volume
yeah volume to take it
how's the shampoo time how was it was it good it was
good yes it was amazing
what score what score out of 10 out of 10
out of ten
oh
no no you win you win I
didn't hear that I'm thinking maybe like 8.5 oh nice what's this
oh dewy OK
아 들어왔나요 음 아 진짜 베이비 페이스인데 귀여워 you look is
much younger than you know with yeah
you without makeup yeah
I look younger but your skin looks just fine
just perfect
I was wearing too heavy makeup
too heavy makeup
아기처럼 해주세요 정말 어 알겠습니다 신생아처럼 ㅎㅎ 진짜 러블리하게
해야겠다 응 밝게 응 밝은
것도 브라이트
네 밝게 하는 게 이쁠 거 같긴 해요 오늘 메이크업에는 응
that makes it look very Korean
OK I wanna look I wanna look Korean
I wanna accentuate my Korean features 근데 지금 Korean 같다
it's good
oh it makes me look I feel like it makes you look younger almost
what are you doing after
um I'm having dinner with my mom
OK yeah oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh my God how about your childhood hmm
that I wonder
when I was young I think she had a hard time
with like my body type and
I think you know I'm her daughter so she expects
me to look maybe a certain way when I was young but now she's more
she's she understands me
so much better now but I was very influenced by western culture
oh oh
oh
you know so
and she's very influenced by Korean culture
hmm but now I think my mom likes a little bit of both
hmm she's very open minded ah
I love it
언니 레이철이
이거 화장 안 하니까 너무 애기 얼굴이
어 애기 얼굴이에요 애기 같죠 어 애기
얼굴 같네 베이비 페이스에요 완전
베이비 페이스 맞아요 귀여워요 네 피부도 너무 좋고 피부도 너무 좋고
완전 애기 같아요
애기 키울 때 너무 좋았어요 미국 와
갖고 제 제가 열한 열 십 개월 때인가 왔거든요 여기 와서 낳은 아니
고국에서 났어요 한국에서
그 순천에서 태어나라고 아 나 자기 순천 베이비라고 아 순천
베이비 어 엄마랑 이렇게 아직도 같이 여행 다니고 보통은 안 그러잖아요
애기예요 애기 하면 너무 이렇게
예뻐 세라니 있으면 마음이 정하대요 ㅎㅎ 귀여워 엄마
oh
hi hi Cynthia
hi hi Cynthia hi how are you how are you
hello Cynthia hello
nice to see you nice to see you too yes please follow me
어 신시아 어디가 바로 들어가 아 신시아 야
so oh oh Hulk oh big Hulk
that's a sweet Hulk please have a seat
so Cynthia
so let's get started about your consultation
um do you have any like a before we start any allergies or concerns
no allergies
a little concerned I definitely I have like some acne
that happens it's very frustrating
hi my name is Cynthia Gray I am 34 and I'm an actor and a writer
in New York City
a little bit of changing your eyebrow brow area
yeah they
they need some work I'll shine your eyes right
yeah is that what you want
yeah yes
I can see the difference between
you know after makeover
so let's start get started with your hair
yeah yeah
thank you for coming thank you for having me
hi salon
yes OK
this is the time
ㅎㅎ 아 선생님 바로 하시는 거예요 네 메이크업
자리 없어서 아 아니면 마무리를 하고
저기 하는 게 어떨까 싶어 가지고
아이 그래야 될 거 같아요 아 기다리라고 오
빨리 정리를 하고 그냥 여기 알겠어요 붙여서 얘기할게요 그거는
Ciao ci vediamo
아 내가 이렇게 스케줄을 잘못 짜서 이게
엉켰나 어 아니 뭐가 뭐 뭐가 잘못돼서 이렇게
어떻게 이렇게 됐지 혹시
메이크업 먼저 하면 안
돼요 나는 메이크업은 먼저 하고 싶긴 한데 어 물어봐 볼래요 나도
메이크업 먼저 하고 싶긴 한데 예
혹시 그 메이크업 먼저 해도 되나요 저분 첫 번째 분 네 헤어컷 먼저
돼 있긴 한데 네 순서상 네 그렇게
하셔도 돼요 아 네 우선은 그렇게 할게요 네 첫 번째 분이죠 네
I'm so sad why because your makeup is so pretty right now
I did my best you did hahaha oh my God
I think you did I think you did a good job hahaha I don't know
she's here oh yes can you wait for her like 10 minutes
yeah yeah it's alright yeah
sorry for waiting no you're fine don't worry about it I'm so sorry
no you're fine yeah no I'm used to being on set for like
16 hours like this is wow
16 hours yeah
we get really long days over here
so like this is fun
no you're totally fine okay
quiet quiet
maybe slower our speed I don't have anything until eight PM
so like literally however long you need alright
thank you if you need anything
just call me OK
yes I'll do
thank you thank you
야 끝나면 알려
알려줘요 머리 아직 안 했죠 머리 안 했지 머리 와서 같이 할게요
네 잠깐만 저기로 가시 가야
될 거 같아요 네 갈게요 감사합니다 I can do it
I just straighten straighten your hair pasty first yeah
again looks great
I'm a plus size model
I'm very used to doing like American style hair American style makeup
I wanted to try something new
specifically Korean beauty to enhance my features that are Korean
I never did it this way before
그디가 되게 영무드로 변했어요 진짜
이쁘다 허 예뻐 되게 청순해 오우 you look like like
high school oh no hahaha
I'm a brand new 진짜 brand new 세상에 처음
봐요 다른 사람이야
OK 갑시다 갑시다 오케이 갑시다 yes 아 yes
oh it's a close eye yes okay hahaha
don't look at her yeah yeah there's a secret there's something secret
just like it's just like
OK she's coming really really I'm so excited
oh my God oh my God oh my God
너무 이쁘다
hi it's me someday I might know
when pushing on my back
I was wondering your is many times hair cutting is here
this is elegance elegance
then half part is in sleep
yeah in the section
wow do you like this song
I do yeah
yeah it's so cool
I'm gonna throw the swimming style
Korean loves egg exercise
give the point the lower eye area
it's so you do it cuter
take it oh
I never did it this way before
it's my moment
너무 이쁘다 너무 이뻐 ㅎㅎ 어디가 어디가 ㅎㅎ
아이 화장이 되게
청순하지 않아요 아 진짜 이쁘다 정말 딸 정말 이쁘죠
아까 처음 여기 왔을 때랑 완전 다르다 I'm officially a 한국
officially officially officially
thank you so much
이제 들어오셔도 될 것 같습니다 바로 응 나다 아 선생님 어우
어우 어우 아 이제 이제 회의하고 오겠습니다
ah sorry for waiting no it's fine
have a seat
여기 좀 더운가 응 아 이게 빠졌네 음 이거 봐
you want some drink 아 안 그래도 땡기던데
thank you for your patience thank you very thank you
of course it's your love what you waited so long is it okay oh yeah
sorry about that no you're fine
you're so sweet thank you for understanding of course
well I so many times I'm on set for 15 or 16 hours so
this is nothing okay thank you thank you for listening of course
I've been into K pop
like it's the only thing I've listened to for about 14 years
oh I just I saw a music video and I was like oh they're dancing
I really like this and very quickly then that was all I listened to
and we tried to learn the routines in my bedroom
not very well oh my God
so cool yeah
so like tonight um
you're so talented oh yeah
wow but I
I finally have a dance team and we're recording like Jenny tonight so
oh Jinja yeah
today uh
yeah at Times Square we're gonna
we're gonna do the whole dance 잠깐만 오늘 촬영 있다고
for the style for today I really wanted to look like an idol
because tonight
my dance team we are doing our first recording ever in Times Square
we're doing a dance
cover and so I thought it would be really good to have like hair and makeup
that really fit the vibe
Jenny Jenny Jenny Jenny
but have you ever met
오늘 아
야 타임스퀘어에 우리가 너무 우리가 너무 지루해 잠깐만 오늘 촬영
있다고 큰일났다 집중해 포커스 포커스 오케이
알았어 알았어요 오늘 지금
아주 중요한 일이 있었네 그러면 진짜 이쁘게 해 줄게요 trust me
I believe in you
you gonna be so cool on the makeup with the makeup yes so
don't worry
how much do you sweat yeah many a lot yeah when you do dancing yeah
oh I'm gonna use this this is magic
yeah usually K pop idol'cause you do you know what's the bomb
it's a festival yeah they they use this oh yeah
cause I've always wondered I was like why how does your makeup
look so perfect as you're like yes
I'm gonna use tonight for tonight oh
thank you thank you thank you
it helps to last the makeup yeah
oh much better yeah okay
하 웨이 ㅎㅎ
because 감 잡기가 힘들었어요 사실은 처음에 왜냐면 착하신 분들 특징
어 저 다 좋아요 어 괜찮아 너 원하는 대로 해 나 오픈이야 뭐
이렇게 그러니까 음 그래
아 뭘 쓸지 막 피치 색깔로 꾸며 볼까 막 이렇게 하는데 아
do you have any reference
아 아 I think you want totally the a little bit edge yeah and then
완전 샌 언니 그런 한국 아이돌
느낌만 쫙 저장을 해 온 거예요 감을 확 잡았어요
OK not lovely right
yeah I think'cause just'cause it's such an attitude oh oh song
okay okay good
it'll be better be bored okay so okay
I'm gonna use eye primer
I've never done my eyeliner like this with the bottom
oh some glitter
I use this the real K pop idol yes
it's for the ending pose yeah bling bling
아 예쁘다 응 아 오우
you have a like a glitter under your eyes oh my God you have to go to
the club or so whatever
아 오늘 진짜 근데 촬영한다 그래 가지고 타임
스케일에서 잘 어울릴 거 같아요 그 춤 촬영한다고 눈이 약간 헤더베이
닮아가지고 약간 수진
아니고 메이크업 하니까 되게 많이 되게 많이 닮았어요 엄청 닮았어요
이거 찍어 찍어 줘야지 이거 신 신시아 폰이야 혼자 와 가지고
음악이 없으니까 되게 그래 맞아 다 넣어주세요 아 맞아 음악이 없었어
oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh so beautiful
오 옷까지 갈아입으니까 너무 이뻐
그래야 돼 사진 찍어야
돼 마음에 드세요 아 이런 옷도 어울리네요 그러니까
프렌치 스타일이에요 너무 이뻐 너무 이뻐
I love you
프렌치 시크 느낌
나는 웨이브 있죠 약간 부스스 하면서 그 다음에 한국에서
유행한 시술로 맹을 좀 믹스 이로 해서 음 아우 진짜 이쁘다 근데
음
I'm so lonely
yeah I really wanna stay all day with you
there were a couple of times in the middle of uh
getting my makeup done oh who's that oh that's me hahaha
like I genuinely did not recognize myself
don't pause take it to the course
Jenny Jenny I think I really like Jenny Jenny
haters that don't really like Jenny
Jenny cause they can never ever be Jenny Jenny Jenny but I
today's experience was just really great everything
was I don't know just even even more fun than I anticipated
but have you ever met
OK thank you so much see you next time thank you yeah definitely
bye yeah bye so much
넌 밥을 먹은 거야 먹어야지 밥 먹자 밥 먹으세요 밥 좀 하시고요
자 밥
먹 밥 먹어 볼까 죄송합니다 배고프셨죠
저기 앉아서 먹으면 비우 되게 좋아요 거기에 딱 그
앉아 가지고 딱 다리 펴고 먹으면 리워크 같아요 그래요 잘 먹겠습니다
참고로 고기 좀 찢겨요 그래요
어
손님 왔어요 어 손님 왔어요 손님 왔네 hi thank you
oh hello nice to meet you you
too
thank you so much it's beautiful
just have a seat have a seat
thank you hi
Catherine yes
yes Catherine Madonna
I know it's you but it's
hello
Lisa hi you
so we have a four uh
five kind of uh
welcome drinks
the first one is just regular Americano and the green tea
we also have a K Idol you know drink
it's nice
and the next one is K Banana latte
oh yeah
so I've seen this online right
yeah it's so popular
yeah everyone goes right into
you know convenience store and get the banana milk and just make it
I just really yes
so it's it's ours
I know they all sound delicious
this is one of our you know
signature drink and the last one is for you
is for you we have some yogurt
do you have like a she loves yogurt
she loves yogurt yes
that would be perfect thank you
so maybe try this don't go out there
banana banana milk
what are you may I do the Idol
Idol K Idol
green tea green
yes please
green tea yes
OK perfect thank you
I'm OK Johnny
종혁이가 와야 되는데 저기 혹시
지금 드링크 만들 사람 종혁이 한 명 받아라고 해 주시죠
종혁이 형 네
만들어요
아니 먹어 에 먹어봐 아 저거 도와달라 그래가지고 여기서 드링크 하나
만들어 달라 하시는데
아 뭐 만들어야 되는데 아니 저거 만 저기 꿀 록차랑 뚱바라떼 그리고
애기는 요구르트
손 높여 차 한번 갖고 안 깠대 아니 그거 가져갔어요 아 아 너 거구나 ㅎㅎ
아 미안
아 아
너꺼구나 ㅎㅎ 아 미안 미안해
먹으려고 뺏었는데 아 나는 애기 꺼 뜯는 줄 알고 뺏을 뻔 했네
this is our consultation room beautiful thank you
what we are do going to do is
talking and know each other
uh before we start do you have any allergies or concerns
uh when I was growing up I struggled with acne
and then also like a lot of people with darker skin um
we have hyperpigmentation oh so like you could have
a blemish for like two days but a Mark for like
months or year it's like not fair OK
you're kind of like afraid of it a little yeah
I'm afraid of things that are
more aggressive but I'm curious about things like
well I don't know very much about K
Beauty but what I know is it's more about like
natural beauty taking a really good care of your skin like
bringing out that glow and I'm like that sounds amazing haha
yes that's true
OK so oh come on excuse me hi nice to meet you I'm Leo
I'm your Leo how are you today join us hahaha
nice to meet you
you as well so now we are going to talk about is makeover totally okay
let me just
what's your style yeah what's my style okay so my style is very much
informed by the two places I've lived
I grew up in Southern California very simple natural yes
hair is soft skin is fresh
you know you're just
you might go to the beach after dinner
that life yeah
but then now here I've lived in New York for over 20 years
which is about Polish pulling it together
knowing what's cool so I feel like I like that mix
like I like kind of like soft flattering hair
makeup that makes you look glowy
yeah but not trying too hard
cause then that's the California side
the effortlessness of California
but the like polish but your identities
so it means exactly it means not too glam right exactly yeah
like I love highlighter I love blush
I love like pretty lashes that aren't too heavy
you know and that's when I think about K beauty
that's kind of what I think about
like just that beauty that's like fresh
that's okay beauties
so any plans today um
I think I'm going to spend some time with my family
and then I think my husband and I are going on a date later
so yeah I'm very excited
so let's get started okay
thank you so much I'm excited
oh nothing can stop me I will
I'm feeling lofty oh I got the X Factor
let's go to hair John 1st OK sounds good
your daughter is so cute oh thank you
hi baby
you having a snack you say quick hi
hi my baby
can you have your banana
hi baby
hi baby you're dying
yes hi
I'll see you soon my love hi
hello hello
how was how was it
it was lovely I had some delicious snacks
just have a seat thank you so much
okay let's do the skincare first
okay sounds good
I will put this mask back
okay
this is good for the hydration
have you ever tried the K Beauty products
I not for real
for real
I've done like little sheet masks you get in like the American Mall
like not a real K Beauty salon
okay
this is gel mask pack
so looks like a gel
oh good for hot weather
have you ever tried this kind of mask bag
no I've never tried it before
but it feels nice already
it feels like squid
yeah
little calamari
calamari
maybe 10 minutes okay sounds good
아 맞을까
아 근데 자식 이분 오신다고 했을 때 진짜 긴장을 너무 했어요 왜냐하면은
이렇게 흑인 분을 메이크업 해드릴 기회가 일단 많지 않잖아요 이거 너무
막 하 이거
너무 막 짜침이 어떡하지 내가 했을 때 에이 그런 느낌 들었어요 고민
진짜 걱정했어요
우리 성함이 레지나 레지나님 캐서린 와 나 진짜 이분
진짜 잘해야 되는데 아이고 이거는 마지막으로 가주신 분
있잖아요 잘해야 돼 캐서린
so challenging 아 진짜 there will use more or like say
맛있을까 짜잔 오 와우
this is my room
gorgeous yes it's like a dream room hahaha a dream room yeah hahaha OK
and let's do the eye makeup oh we go to the foundation so is it is it
uh the right foundation colour you usually use
so you so it looks similar okay
yeah and I will mix it
yes yeah
cause this one looks closer to my concealer
your concealer yeah
and this one is the base right
I think so yeah this one is base
오케이 파운데이션 컬러 고르는 거부터 시작해서 또 현장에서
이것저것 믹스해서 올리는데 그게 진짜 너무 걱정됐어요 피부톤이
아 진짜 아 이거 먹을 수 있게
해 줘 시원해져 나 시원해져 아 이게 너무 어려워
filling up this corner let it
oh hey no way the top the cute
don't try to stop me
Lisa is very good girl oh
yes she's so talented look at your face oh glowing yes
got a clean slate yeah I love it
손 잘 맞춘 거 같아요 음 걱정했는데
그니까 뭔가 이렇게 달라 보이지 않고 되게 착 붙는 거 같아
완전 예 소밀착 ㅎㅎ
잘 기다려 줘야 될 텐데 지금까지는 아주 좋은데 오케이 렛츠
두 더 메이크 아이 메이크업
오케이
what do you think with it I think it's match with your dress I do too
이 쉐도우 컬러는 이런 점으로 보통 이런 의상이랑 잘 맞춰야
된다 매치를 시켜야 된다 물론 톤
온 톤 일 필요는 늘 없지만
그래도
뭔가 이 어울리는 컬러를 항상 매치를 해야 되는 게 중요하거든요 그래서
항상 의상을 먼저 보는 거예요 근데 의상 컬러를 봤더니
어 너무 예쁜 블루 드레스인데 딱 그냥
너무 매치 된다 되겠다 이 블루 블루 했을 때 너무 예쁘겠다
nice oh that's pretty is it good
you like yeah
I love it it's so like subtle yeah
like you have to look closely
look at the mirror
is it too much or I think it's subtle subtle
yeah cause look
if I'm like this you can't even tell yeah
it's like a little bit it's like when I'm right right
and after the lashes yeah
it goes really well I think it'll be yeah cute
wow you're really good with the blue
who knew hahaha
okay let's do
here I have every lash oh yeah
here I have
I think this is gonna be good on you too
but it's super light maybe this one maybe looks good yeah
let's let's just pass it okay pass
boses
0 please
hmm
I don't know but it looks light to me really
really light yeah
maybe this one is super light
like this it is very light
what if you wanna try 1 up
one up yeah yeah
too light
let's try this one more thick thicker
yeah thicker one
let's look at these
it's like I want in between
but I can't tell but I think
let's try another one hmm
아 근데 사실 되게 어렵던 게 이제 요청 사항 중에 투 글램은
또 아니야 아이 나 아이 어
I Love Natural 인데
또 투 글램은 안 돼 그 미들 글램이라는 거예요 그 약간
꾸안꾸를 원하신다는 거예요 그리고 또 뭔가
Natural 한 느낌을 더 좋아하신다는 건
이 어디를 맞춰야 되지 어느 선이지 이게 꾸밈 단계 몇 단계지 이게
너무 어려운
거예요
저 레쉬 좀 가져갈게요 선생님 이거 해
봐야겠다 딴 다른 모세 맞지 똑같은 거야 공사잖아 이거
공사잖아 이거 해 볼게요 이
레오야 이거 두 개 똑같은 거라고 응 아 이거
봐요 여기 넘버를 보면 돼 여기 위에 아
그렇구나 어 공사 번호는 피하고 지금 네가 십 번이랑 공사 번 생겼어
what about this one so light and natural OK
OK really really light OK yeah close eyes please OK
open eyes please oh these are the ones
do you feel okay yeah yeah
it's a light yeah okay
힘을 좀 빼려고 노력했어요 그래서 좀 내추럴한 거
붙여달라는데 한국 통역 수업이에요 그랬더니
밀도는 좀 있는데 굉장히 라이트해서 편안하면서도 좀
길이감은 좀 적당한 요런 걸 해
드리니까 어 되게 내추럴하게 디패스로
I love it look very nice
I think it looks really good I think it looks so nice
Mommy
here Mommy
my dog is so pretty Mami Mami is so pretty you look
like Bunny yes yes bunny
are you mommy
a big bunny there she's playing with the little bunny oh where is it
oh the big bunny I can give you you know
thank you this is gift for you
good night Bunny good night
I'm all booked out
어우 이거
완전 물결인데 왜 이거 아 이거 살짝 약간
느낌만 주는 거야 느낌을 그니까 느낌만 주고 있는 거예요
아 또 나 리사가 울까 봐 아 아니 아니
어제 어제 애기가 어 예스터디 어제가 예스터디 예스터데이 a baby cry
oh yeah because Leo told me
oh no she's not my mom and she just ran away
it's really been a long time since she wore makeup
no no no
1 2 3
it's Mommy
makeup on my face makeup on mommy's face
do you like it
do you think mommy looks pretty
no
yes oh
we already did my mom oh
of course thing that's so funny
it's very is an amazing day
Lisa's not angry with it Lisa's yeah
are you ready Lisa ready
please please please
come here come here
oh he's
coming he's coming
he's coming he's coming
so I feel like I like that mix
like I like kind of like soft flattering hair
makeup that makes you look glowy
yeah but not trying too hard
cause then that's the California side
coming your mum is coming coming
oh your mum is coming
oh my God oh my God
and we could be such a sigh
oh oh
oh oh just let go
oh my God
oh my
God wow
you look gorgeous
it's hard work
that's okay that's okay
do you like it yeah
oh thank you
yeah oh
it's wedding day one more try
thank you
oh I'm so grateful
thank you you're so beautiful
thank you you guys are so talented
thank you so much like a different woman
these are our small gifts for you
oh my gosh thank you so much
yeah some products and
Korean traditional like a hand fan
you know it's folding yes
that's perfect I prepared for you
oh thank you so much
thank you it's such a beautiful experience
and I feel very beautiful and very k beauty wow
that's nice one
I have a baby daughter who I love
but that means that my beauty and makeup routine is like what is fast
like you know
there's no experimentation
there's no taking your time
you know so I think part of me doesn't go over with hair and makeup
cause it's really who I am
but I also think it's nice to be reminded that like
you could do something special
or you could take a risk or you could stand out a little bit um
I just I feel really happy I feel really grateful
thank you so much thank you
bye Lisa thank you so much
thank you bye have a nice day
아우 어떻게 한 번도 안 울고 애기가 에 장하다 장해 장하다 응
아 어서 오세요 단장이 오신 것을 환영합니다 그 뭐냐 뉴스에 나오시지
않으셨어요 아유 그 너무 반가워요 아유 버클리 음대 사람 처음 봐 너무
멋있어 장난 아니에요 응
my name is Emma Benson
I'm an executive chef of a restaurant in New York
my life is just cooking it's kitchen
I've never been like take care of myself 머리가
너무 없어가지고 지금 걱정이에요 하드 미션이
왔네 오늘 굿 아이디어 그러니까
what about like
색신이 커라기도 한 것 같기도 하고 너무 어려웠어요 사실 나 나대로 가요
방법이 없네 아니 아니 찾아봐야죠 방법을 이분 정말 완벽하게 해서
보내드려야겠다라는 생각밖에 없어요 일단만 일단 미워서
머리를 되게 곱둘려서 했어요 정말 풀 글램 하자 우와 진짜 예쁘다
우와 대박 우
this is the moment this is the moment